If I've already made videos about solving
my clients' problems, how can I move
through the plateau
and find new content ideas?
Motherfucker, I've been doing the same 10,
15 videos
over and over again for 10 years, bro.
It's not about new,
it's about making it better.
Imagine this,
if I go to your social media profile right
now, and I say, I get a
fucking gun out, and I go,
"Show me the best fucking video you've
ever done." And
you go, "It's this one." I go,
"Not just views.
Which one got you the most fucking
clients?" You go, "Oh, it
was this one." I go,
"Cool. Can you make it better?
If you don't make it better,
I'm going to kill your
whole fucking family." And you're like,
"Oh, yeah, I can make-" Well, go and make
it better then. Because if
that video got you 10 fucking clients
before, if you
make it a better version of it,
you might get 15.
And then you go, "Okay, now what?" Well,
let's find the second-best video you've
ever done and make it better.
All you ever do is just keep redoing them.
If you go to my YouTube, most of them,
or even my Instagram, it's the same
fucking videos over and over again.
Think about this.
Imagine you see a skyline.
There's a big building in there. You go,
"I'm going to build a bigger one." So you
build a bigger one.
Someone's going to come along and go,
"Do you know what we're
going to do?" Go on.
"Build a bigger one." They build a fucking
bigger one.
Then some other cunts come along,
and they go,
"We should build a bigger one than
them two." Build the next one. Now,
all of these people out-competing each
other,
the Burj Khalifa will no longer be the
tallest building in the world within
probably 10, 15, 20 years, whatever.
You just have to keep skyscraping all of
your own videos.
So,
you don't just make a video on everything,
then move on because you are
accelerating and learning at such a
different rate.
Your creativity over time compounds way
bigger than an ETF.
How can I find new content ideas?
Go back and make them fucking better, bro